<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="project">
        <item>routing  game</item>
        <item>ramp metering game</item>
        <item>ring road</item>
        <item>ring road two lanes</item>
        <item>clover leaf</item>
        <item>cellular automata</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="projectName">
        <item>routing</item>
        <item>ramp_metering</item>
        <item>ringroad_1lane</item>
        <item>ringroad_2lanes</item>
        <item>cloverleaf</item>
        <item>startStop_all_ca</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="projectPath">
        <item>sim/games/</item>
        <item>sim/games/</item>
        <item>sim/buildingBlocks/</item>
        <item>sim/buildingBlocks/</item>
        <item>sim/buildingBlocks/</item>
        <item>sim/bookScenarioStartStop/</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="infoScenario">
        <item>            Objective:\n\n
            Switch the routing recommendation to use the capacity
of the two roads optimally.\n\n
What makes the game interesting:\n\n
Externally given:
\n\n
A fixed traffic demand curve with a "rush-hour" peak. The main road ("freeway") has a road-works
bottleneck. At peak demand, the inflow exceeds the freeway
capacity. It is set such that even the best player should not manage
to avoid all breakdowns. The capacity of the "village bottleneck"
is half the capacity of one freeway lane (or less).</item>
        <item>Objective\n\n
            Delay the jam on the freeway by controlling the inflow with the
metering traffic light. Simultaneously avoid waiting times
behind the light. And definitely have a look at the spillover to the
secondary road.\n\n
What makes the game interesting:\n\n
Control the traffic light metering the ramp inflow to the freeway. No
yellow phases and no minimum green times apply here, i.e., one can let
pass a single vehicle at a time. 
\n\n
Externally given:
\n\n
A fixed traffic demand curve on the freeway and the secondary road 
with a "rush-hour" peak. A fixed percentage of vehicles on the
secondary road (e.g., 50%) turns right and enters the freeway via the traffic
light. The traffic flow is set so that congestion occurs on the
freeway if the traffic light is left green all the time.</item>
        <item>What makes the scenario interesting:\n\n
            traffic jam.
            Externally given:\n\n
            IDM with noise</item>
        <item>What makes the scenario interesting:\n\n
            traffic jam.
            Externally given:\n\njam with lane change</item>
        <item>            Objective:\n\n
            What makes the scenario interesting:\n\n
            Complex road network. Just a perfamance test for your Android device.
            Externally given:\n\n</item>
        <item>MovSim is a scientic research tool. The objective is how to model basic traffic situations.
            \n\n
            What makes the scenario interesting:\n\n
            Here you can see a different approach to model vehicles. In the previous scenaris we used a car-following model.\n Here cellular automata are used. You should \"see\" the difference.\n\n The advantage of the cellular automata models: they are faster.\n\n
            The displayed models in this start-stop scenario are:\n\n
            Nagel-Schreckeberg\n
            Barlovic\n
            Kerner-Klenow-Wolf</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="highscoreRouting">
        <item>Wow, King of the road! You really have figured this out.</item>
        <item>Fantastic time! But still improvable.</item>
        <item>Pretty good. Much better then any navigation system you can buy. But not much to be proud of.</item>
        <item>You are as bad as an expensive navigation system. Trx again.</item>
        <item>You are as bad as a standard navigation system.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="highscoreRampMetring">
        <item>Wow, King of the road! You really have figured this out.</item>
        <item>Fantastic time! But still improvable.</item>
        <item>Pretty good.</item>
        <item>Not too bad. But not that good either. Try again.</item>
        <item>Give it a thought.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>